a3trading.com 2018-04-17

# A3 Trading - Privacy Policy

A3Trading respects each individual's right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take great pride in maintaining the privacy and therefore the loyalty of each individual client, by providing the required security. The provisions of this notice apply to both former and current customers.

#### 1\. Personal Information

In order to provide you with the very best service, when you apply to become a A3Trading customer or open a live account, we will ask you for personal information. This information will assist us in evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, keeping you informed about products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing you with a better customer experience.

#### 2\. Required Information May Include:

Application Information – full name, address, birth date, identity − social security number, occupation, assets and income.

Transaction Information – Information about your transactions with us and/or our affiliates, and records of past communications. These may include your account balances, trading activity, past inquiries and our responses.

Verification Information – This may be required to verify your identity, and may include passport or driver’s license.

Note: Anti-Money Laundering ("AML") regulations and the USA Patriot Act requires financial institutions to collect information and take action where necessary, in order to verify a customer’s identity.

Note: A3Trading does not intentionally collect information from persons under thirteen years of age.

#### 3\. The Use of Cookies

We use a technology called "cookies", which enables us to provide you with a better experience in using our website by sending small text files from our servers to your computer. These cookies do not track your private information.

#### 4\. Sharing Information:

**a. Affiliates**

We may share some or all of the personal information described above with our affiliates in order to service client accounts or inform clients of new products and services. Our affiliates may include companies controlled or owned by us, as well as companies which have an ownership interest in our company. Our affiliates maintain the privacy of your information in the same manner and to the same extent as A3Trading, and in accordance with this privacy policy.

**b. Third Parties**

A3Trading does not disclose your personal information to third parties, except as described in this privacy policy. Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform support services for your account or facilitate your transactions with A3Trading. These companies may include those that provide professional, legal or accounting services to A3Trading. Non-affiliate companies that assist A3Trading in providing services are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it. In addition, they are obligated to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes dictated by A3Trading.

A3Trading may disclose a customer’s personal information to a third party in order to fulfill their instructions or pursuant to express consent. It is important to us that you know that A3Trading will not sell your personal information.

**c. Regulators**

A3Trading may disclose your personal information to third parties as permitted by, or in order to comply with applicable laws and regulations. This may include disclosing personal information in order to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies, as may be necessary to protect our property or rights.

**d. Merger or Bankruptcy**

A3Trading is obliged to maintain customer information according to its incorporation laws. In the event of a merger, the information will merge along with the company. In the event of bankruptcy, different legal statuses shall apply in accordance with its incorporation laws and its recordkeeping requirements

**e. Payment Information**

A3Trading does not keep, in any form, customer payment information.

#### 5\. Failure to Provide Personal Information

You have a choice to supply any or all of the personal information required. However, missing information may result in our being unable to open or maintain your account and /or to provide you with our services

#### 6\. Opt Out

Should you choose to have your name and personal data removed from our database, you can do so by sending an email to CUSTOMER.SERVICE@A3TRADING.COM. Clients data is retained for 7 (seven) years after they cease to be a client.

#### 7\. Amendments

Any amendments to our privacy policy that affect the personal information of users collected on our website will be notified to the users, within a reasonable time, via email. Users will have a choice whether or not we use the information in a different manner. Any amendments made by us that do not affect personal information will be posted on our website. Clients data is retained for 7 (seven) years after they cease to be a client.

#### 8\. Mailing Information

Whether you wish to talk to us about our privacy policy or any other issue, the professional team at A3Trading is available to assist you 24/7. Please feel free to contact us via phone and e-mail. You can also or use our chat facility to IM a customer service representative.

Company Registered Address: Commodius FX LTD, Law Partners House, Kumul Highway, Port Vila, Vanuatu

Tel: +442038073524  

E-mail: [CUSTOMER.SERVICE@A3TRADING.COM](mailto:CUSTOMER.SERVICE@A3TRADING.COM "E-mail")

The purpose of this risk disclaimer is to inform users of the potential financial risks involved in trading in foreign currencies. The transaction or operations in the Forex or fx markets does involve a substantial degree of risk, and should not be undertaken until the user has carefully evaluate whether their financial situation is appropriate for such transactions. Trading may result in a substantial or complete loss of funds and therefore should only be undertaken with risk capital. Any information included in this website does not constitute an offer of services for clients residing in any jurisdictions where such offer is not authorized. **A3Trading** is a brand name operated by Commodius FX Limited, PO Box 1276, Port Vila, Vanuatu. Clearing services are provided by Wanakena Ltd, Agias Zonis 4, Palatino Building, Flat/Office 202, 3027 Limassol, Cyprus.
